Leone, stop! We don't have time
for something so unimportant!
Unimportant? There's nothing
more important to me right now!
I see. You've grown.
I won't let you get away!
Leone!
Don't move.
I'd prefer you stay out of this.
We don't want to hurt the
daughter of the Arcia family.
My father may be the Chancellor,
but I'm only an academy student,
and yet they know who I am...
Just who are the Bloodchain Brigade?
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 10    The Plan to Attack a Highlander
Mother and Father are gone!
But for the people of Almen
who were left behind...
I can never forgive you!
And if you lose Almen,
you'll have nothing else left!
The royal court has decided to offer up
Almen to the Hierarch Highlanders
to restore relations with them.
But why would they do that?
It's outlived its purpose as a place from
which to monitor the frozen Prismer.
I suppose they feel they have
nothing to lose by offering it up.
That's not right, though!
Where's the justice in that?
If you must rage against someone,
direct your ire toward your foolish king
who'd hand over his own people
to curry favor with Highlanders.
The Hyral Menas will be
handed over in four days.
The Highlander emissary will come by boat.
We'll attack and kill the
emissary when they arrive.
Our only enemies are the Highlanders, who
are trying to steal the very land from us.
You're telling us your plan?
What are you plotting?
If you'd like to try something of your own,
feel free to take advantage
of the chaos we'll cause.
But don't get in our way.
And you think we'll just believe you?
That's up to you.
Now, goodbye.
Brother!
But I... No matter what your reason is...
Do what you think is best.
Nobody will stop you.
But... You've grown.
I can't do a thing for you,
but that makes me happy.
Keep it up.
Leone...
We need to head back and tell everyone.
So you're saying that if we don't stop them,
the Highland will take Ripple?
And the town of Almen, to boot!
That's just not right!
Yes. We have to do something.
But what?
I have a plan.
I see.
That would work!
But it's too reckless!
Every time Chris says something,
it's either reckless or insane.
Yeah...
Agreed.
In a sense, they trust you, Inglis.
We'll go with Inglis's idea, then.
I'll get things started on my end first!
Four Days Later
Wh-What is this?
What do you mean?
They're maid outfits, of course.
They're going to infiltrate the court
under the guise of part-time servants.
These maid outfits are great, huh?
Yup!
Principal Miliera,
was there really no better way?
I thought it was a great idea!
One that takes full advantage
of their cuteness!
It'll be okay, Silva!
When the Bloodchain Brigade
comes to attack, we'll defeat them!
While protecting the king
and the Highlander emissary.
Don't forget that.
Okay!
Good grief...
When are they handing over Ripple?
Right after the ceremony at the court.
We wanted a little more time,
but the royal guards weren't having it.
But at the start they were saying,
"Hand her over immediately!"
This is a major victory!
All thanks to Silva.
I have a brother in the Royal Guard.
I wasn't sure about going to him for help,
but it didn't feel like we had a choice.
While the royal guards are
busy protecting the court,
Silva and I will feed Ripple our mana,
making her summon magicite beasts
until there aren't any more left to summon.
Then there'll be no reason
to take her back to the Highland.
It's a little crazy, but it'll work!
It's not a little crazy. It's insane.
But we don't have a choice.
I'll be counting on you two.
For Ripple's sake, too.
Wh-What?
Silva, do you like Ripple?
Don't be ridiculous!
Oh, my...
You don't have to hide it!
I do not! It would be most improper
to think of a Hyral Menas that way.
I do respect her deeply...
Respect?
When I was young, she saved my life.
There was a sudden rain
of Prism Flow one day.
A friend and I were attacked
by a magicite beast.
We both ran... and he died protecting me.
I was weak, and so he,
a Runeless, had to die.
Just as I thought it was all over,
Ripple saved me.
She held me as I cried, and she said...
Get stronger.
For the sake of your friend
who protected you.
And so you can protect dozens—
no, hundreds of times as many people more.
Those words are what made me who I am today.
I trained hard every day, so that I
could be someone who protects others.
So he didn't hate the Runeless after all.
He wanted to keep them from danger, and he
was willing to sacrifice his own life for it.
I'm sorry for making you
remember something like that.
It was a long time ago.
Don't worry about it.
Is the reason you use a gun Artifact...
Yes. I thought it would make it
easier to fight alongside Ripple.
That's wonderful...
I'm sure Ripple will be very happy.
Ripple remembered Silva.
She looked upset... I don't know why.
No, it's probably because I'm not
strong enough for her to rely on me.
That's not...
Either way, we need to carry out the plan.
I don't want Ripple to be taken
from our country yet.
Yes. And that's why we need
to do our best tomorrow!
Leave it to us, Silva!
Right. I'll do my best on my end, too.
No, I'd like to meet up with you guys
and join the fight, so take your time.
Just how obsessed
are you with fighting?
New girls! Come help over here!
Okay!
It looks great!
The food at the court's
really something else.
Rani, you ate too much.
There's no shrimp left.
And just how much meat
are you going to eat, Chris?
I'm eating a little from everything
so they don't find out!
It's a waste, too!
When the Bloodchain Brigade comes,
nobody's going to get to eat this food.
Nobody can know about the attack.
We don't want to talk about it and have
them think we're co-conspirators.
You say that, but you're
just trying to make sure
you've got as many enemies
to fight as possible, right?
That's right.
Chris...
Well, whatever. Until that
time comes, we have to work!
Oh, the king has arrived!
King Carius!
Hail to the king!
Your Majesty! Your Majesty, King Carius!
The king's got a Special-class rune, huh?
He must be strong.
It'll be easy to protect him.
We don't know that for sure.
If you're doing your job as king,
you won't have any time left to practice.
I know that firsthand.
Today, I'm pleased to welcome
an emissary from the Highland.
They've promised to send a new Hyral Menas,
who will lead our kingdom
to even greater glory.
What about Almen?
Maybe they don't have to
hand it over anymore.
That's not it. At times like these,
you just say the good things, not the bad.
That's kind of sneaky!
Now, let us welcome the emissary.
Everyone, be on your best behavior.
Yes, sire.
Highlander Arch Lord
(Great General) Ivel
Wow, he's cute!
His eyes and hair are such pretty colors.
Yeah.
Allow me to introduce you all.
This is the Highlander emissary, Lord Ivel.
Despite his young age,
he is already a great general.
Oh, is that true?
Then he must be of a higher rank
than a typical emissary.
Emissaries who get sent to the surface
are just low-level foreign officers.
I bear the rank of Arch Lord
and command the Chief Hierarch's armies.
I take it all back. He's not cute at all!
I'm nothing like them.
True.
Wonderful!
It's an honor to see him!
This is a day I'll remember forever!
I don't like this.
Everybody sucking up
to that mean little kid.
Yeah.
Hey, Chris! Pay attention!
This is hilarious!
We get a whole city just for swapping out
one defective Hyral Menas!
You're losing the lives of your fellow men,
you're losing a valuable asset,
and you're still trying to suck up to me!
You're all crazy.
You fools don't realize that
any one of you could be next.
I hate to say it, but he's right.
Yup.
Well, for my part,
it's easier to deal with fools.
Thanks. For being so stupid.
There's no need to thank us, Lord Ivel.
We are fools, as you say.
And I, as king, am the
greatest fool of them all.
I only hope that you will teach us
to be as smart as you.
Please teach us...
I don't want to see this. It's pathetic.
Yeah? It's kinda interesting, though.
Normally, one would respond
to such provocations with anger.
For him to react this way...
Either he's not human, or he has
something he truly believes in.
You're interesting, for a fool.
Magicite beasts!
They're here!
Let's do it, Chris!
Huh?
Who is that girl?
I'm a maid, so it's my job
to clean up the banquet hall!
Rani, you take—
What was that?
I've never seen that attack before.
Seal the exits! Prepare for
an attack from the windows!
Protect the king and the emissary!
Yes, sir!
How obnoxious.
Die!
I can't move...
L-Let me go!
No.
The Highlanders must be stopped
before they take all our homes!
Is he with the Bloodchain Brigade?
Hey. Nobody asked for your help.
Did you think a weakling like him
could so much as scratch me?
My apologies.
Well, it's fine.
Restrain him.
The same light as before...
Chris, are you okay?!
Y-Yeah.
Not much scares you, huh?
Thanks.
Did you do that deliberately?
That's disgusting!
Yeah? If anything's disgusting,
it's inviting someone to a banquet
and then trying to kill them.
N-No! I assure you,
our country was not behind this!
It was the Bloodchain Brigade,
a group of rebels that have been
active in our lands lately...
I'm willing to believe that,
but that's still a problem.
A problem?
Your incompetence put a
Highlander emissary in danger.
How do you intend to atone for that sin?
Please, show mercy!
I, Carius, am prepared
to accept any punishment!
Your Majesty!
No, that's not good enough.
An apology only means something
when it's between two equals.
But the Highland and
the surface aren't equal.
You're just the boss of
a group of cattle we keep.
And an apology from cattle
means nothing.
So...
I'm taking an arm.
Y-Your Majesty!
Damn you!
Even if you're the Highland emissary...
Calm yourselves, everyone!
Anyone who harms the emissary will
be executed in the name of the king!
Y-Yes, sire...
Thank you for your mercy, Lord Ivel.
Your Majesty...
Chris, is this really okay?
Is this really right?
It's not...
That's up to the individual, isn't it?
What you think is right, is right.
Everyone really does have their own ideas.
Some pledge loyalty to the Highlanders,
to keep their people alive.
Others try to become stronger,
to become equals to the Highlanders.
What will come of the contrast between them?
Well, that's for the people
of this era to decide.
Anyway, Rani, we have something
we have to hurry and do.
Excuse me.
We'll try to heal your wound.
Rani.
I'll give it a shot.
It's healing!
This is more difficult
than what she did for Silva...
Rani works hard.
Hey, what are you doing?
We are healing him.
May we continue?
I don't mind.
Thank you.
But I'm going to take someone
else's arm instead.
Now, who's going to offer up
their arm to make me happy?
If my healing comes at
such a cost, I cannot...
Try and take my arm, then!
It'll give me a chance to see
that power up close.
Sure.
Normally, I wouldn't care
about the arm of a Runeless,
but I can't wait to see that smile
on your face turn to a scream.
C-Chris!
It's fine, Rani.
Just keep healing His Majesty.
I look forward to hearing
how you'll shriek in pain.
Yeah, it's not just mana moving.
It's a bunch of different
wavelengths mixed together.
You don't know anything!
Now, here I go!
I won't stop, no matter how much you cry!
What?
H-Hey, that was the same
thing he did before, right?
I'd turned down its power
so he couldn't sense it,
Y-Yeah, but...
but I definitely activated
an Aether Shell just now!
And his power exceeded even that...
I like this maid outfit,
so I'm sorry to see it damaged,
but that was a most impressive display!
Amazing! That was amazing!
D-Damn you!
Maybe it's not that powerful after all?
But it definitely killed the
assassin and took the king's arm!
I see! It's not just mana.
It's similar, but using
something more powerful!
It's Mana Refinement!
It increases the purity
and efficiency of mana!
You surface dwellers shouldn't
be able to defend against it!
But you...
Quality over quantity, right?
If it evolves along that path,
it might catch up to aether someday!
Wonderful!
I can't understand your power at all...
What is that power? Who are you?
Who the hell are you?!
Just a maid. Why?
Damn you...
Don't you dare mock me!
Why? It's not working at all!
Even if you're a child,
I don't think it's a good idea to keep
touching a girl's breasts like that.
Oh, sorry.
Now, continue!
Please, cut off my arm!
Inglis, was it?
You're no maid!
Tell me your true identity!
What are you planning?!
My true identity?
Actually...
I'm a part-time maid! I wanted money
to buy lots of yummy food.
So you're not going to answer me?
Then...
At least show me your power!
Come on! Attack me!
But weren't you the one who wanted
my arm instead of the king's?
Forget that!
Come on! Attack me!
Personally, I'd love nothing more
than to duel you, but...
Stand down.
Even if it's what he wants,
you must not harm a Highlander!
You must...
You really are a dumb animal.
There's no point in trying to suck up to me.
The reason that I, an Arch Lord,
came all the way to the surface
was not to bring you a Hyral Menas
or repair relationships between our nations!
The Chief Hierarch is angry!
One day, this whole country
will be wiped from the map.
Then why did you come here?
Because...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Please go
home,
Highlander!
Comic by Kuromura Moto